Put it on.
>> You have to wear it.
>> Awesome. Exciting day. Oh man, big time.
Thanks everybody for coming out. This is
a really exciting day for the Seahawks
organization.
uh obviously jacks, but uh you know when
you go to when you go to ownership and
you ask for an investment like this, you
always have to be so uh cognizant of of
who the person is and um just so proud
of Jackson, who he is as a person. Your
parents did a great job raising you men
and and uh it's just so fun to like
people forget how young you are, you
know. Um, we could talk about the
player. Obviously, great player. I mean,
he scored 82 touchdowns in 42 games in
6A. Texas is like best football arguably
in the country. His head coach would
argue that it would be it was 84.
>> They had two taken away from him. But,
uh, just a, you know, obviously a young
foundational piece, offensive player of
the year. Uh, but yeah, just we're we're
super excited everybody in the building.
Um, we're all here for you, Jacks. um
you know have been from day one and and
I know you'll you'll uh
>> you're going to be great moving forward.
You're a great teammate, great person.
Uh the city of Seattle's got to be Jack
that he's he's going to be with us for a
long time here. And uh yeah, so with
that, just wanted to thank Jody for her
support, Chuck Arnold, and um Joey Lane
for all those long hours on the phone
with uh with Joel Seagull. And uh yeah,
Mike, you want to?
>> Yeah, I think I think one of the things
that just paints a great picture about
what Jax means to us being a
foundational piece of our football team
and our organization is just we got a
full house here. This is pretty awesome.
You got
>> Yeah.
>> Dang near uh dang near the whole Seattle
Seahawks organization sitting um
supporting JS on this day. So um just
>> just want to emphasize how excited we
are. He's going to be here. He's he's a
foundational piece. He's a cornerstone
of our team.
uh just being able to see his growth
over the two years that we've been here
and I mean man this sky's is the limit
and also like this is the beginning you
know this this is this is a this is
another iteration of of our football
team and Jackson is going to be
obviously a huge part of it and uh where
we want to go and where we want to take
our team and uh I know it's early in his
career but he's already a leader on our
team and and uh and will be for a long
time so we're really excited. Mhm.
Yeah, God is great. You know, I'm just
super blessed. Um, like John said, the
whole organization from top to bottom is
just it's a beautiful thing, you know,
where God puts you puts you in place to
succeed. And, you know, this is home for
me and, you know, for me to be extended,
you know, here for a few more years. Um,
I'm just excited and blessed and I
understand, you know, where my feet are
and understand the opportunity that
that's at stake and um, you know, just
like always ready to attack. Um, have to
thank my family, my father, um, my
mother, um, you know, just how they
raised me. You know, I'm here to serve
others, serve the Lord, and, you know,
whatever, you know, these guys need from
me, they know I'm willing to do. So, um,
you know, there's not enough words to
show my excitement and show my love for
the city and this organization, but you
know, you'll see it on Sunday. So, thank
you.
>> Have you figured out how many cowboy
hats you can buy with?
>> We'll buy a few more, huh? Yeah, we'll
buy a few more. Just a few.
for John and for Jackson. This happened
relatively quickly from what your norm
is for this type of a deal. What do you
attribute that to and no drama and and
how seamless it seemed to be?
>> Yeah, you want me to go?
>> Um, yeah. I mean, it it definitely just
feels good. Like John said, ever since I
got drafted, I just felt the love and,
you know, just really just understanding
me and um it's an honor to to feel that
confidence come from your teammates and
come from, you know, the third floor and
your head coach. And, you know, for us
to get this deal done, you know, speaks
volumes, you know, um definitely just a
little weight off my shoulders and just
to go out there and, you know, let it
fly. So, what does it mean? I mean,
you're the highest paid receiver in the
league and all that. What does that mean
to you? Can I set those kind of tests?
>> Um,
you know, there for me, it's always more
work to be done and there's always
another level to reach and uh you know
um but it is a blessing. You know, you
know, this is a business and you know, I
want to do good business and you know,
that's where we're at right now.
>> Said there's always another level to
reach. Offensive player of the year, won
a Super Bowl, as paid receiver.
>> Yes.
>> What what's next for you? How do you
reach next level?
>> The only thing better than one Super
Bowl is two. So, you know, just just
working to to get there and, you know,
whatever my team needs from me, you
know, I make sure, you know, I get it
done.
>> Mike, you said that uh he's already
become a leader. What are some of those
traits you've seen and then Jax, what
what unfolds now as your leadership
potential?
Well, I I think it's it's unique to see
like that type of dominating performance
on a consistent basis, but also the
humility and like what Jackson is
saying, like his servant leadership that
he provides to our team. He's not the
guy that's breaking every huddle,
everything, you know, every team meeting
and everything like that, but what he
does every day, what type of teammate he
is, um, to the guys in the locker room.
I mean, that that that's, you know, that
speaks volumes and that's, uh, that's
where he does his talking.
Yeah. Oh, sorry. Yeah. I think
relationships is, you know, a huge thing
and I think my teammates know, you know,
building relationship with them
one-on-one. You know, they can come to
me and, you know, we can talk about
anything. You know, just want to be
there for my teammates. And um
yeah, I'll just leave it at that.
>> John, we see it a lot in the NFL where
deals of this size, they often drag out
and sometimes they get messy. This one
seemed like it happened pretty quickly
and it didn't seem like it had any of
that. What can you say about just the
process of getting the deal done?
>> Yeah, I just give, you know, Joey Lane a
ton of credit. We have we've had we've
had a great relationship with with
Jackson's agent Joel Seagull for a long
long time. you know, it's just we're
able to just, you know, keep things in
house, keep it respectful, and and um
you know, uh when you're on the higher
end of these deals that are actually I
don't want to say they're easier, but it
kind of like everybody kind of
recognizes, you know, uh Jack's talent
and his work ethic and like I said, the
person, you know, it's just the part,
you know, like I, you know, I remember
being an intern in 1992 and you know, we
signed Reggie White was like the biggest
he was the first biggest free agent in
NFL history and the Packers had $24
million in the bank and they gave him
14, you know, so like I got to like get
with the times a little bit now, you
know? It's like, okay. And Joey Lane and
uh Joey Schneider helped me out of town
with that.
>> John, you you've historically invested
in the receiver position over the years
that DK and Doug Bald went to Tyler Lock
this deal. But um when you look at the
contracts that you guys have signed with
Jackson and bringing back Rasheed and
Jake Bobo coming back matching that
offer, do you view receiver as a premium
position and what makes it so important
to not just sign the stars but the role
players as well at that position with
them?
>> Yeah, great question. We we uh we value
uh people, you know, not necessarily the
position. So people the competitor uh
how they fit into our organization and
you know it's our constant quest to be a
consistent uh championship caliber
football team. So um we don't really get
into like you know like position uh
specifics. We we just know uh that we
want to be smart and in in the people
and the competitor we're investing in.
Mike, you obviously coached Jack's last
year as well, but coming into whether it
was training camps, was there a point in
practice that you recognize like he's in
for a really big year here?
>> Yes,
it was pretty early. It was pretty
early. I mean just to see
it's there's never like just one play
because of you know like the constant
growth that's required but uh I thought
our our our defense was playing at a at
a high level throughout camp and
throughout the offseason program and we
had a really hard time covering and and
uh to Jax's credit you know his ability
to not just stand in one place and only
be able to do one thing to be able to
move him around understand um how to run
the whole route tree the chemistry
that's required with fam. Um, you know,
that's a lot of work that takes and and
you could see it, you know, coming to
life every day and that's what that was
really exciting.
>> Uh, your brother, uh, spends more time
helping you stuff off the field uh, this
year. What did that mean to you? How did
that help you this season?
>> Yeah, it takes a village. Um, my brother
plays a big role in, you know, getting
stuff done and allowing me to, you know,
focus on things I want to focus on and
build on things and, you know, he's my
right-hand man. So, um, you know, um,
just getting started, too. You know, got
a long ways to go on, you know, the
field and off the field. So, you know,
to have him is a blessing and, um,
something I don't take for granted.
>> I know you probably have a long list,
but what are a couple of traits your dad
taught you?
>> Traits really, I mean, first and
foremost, hard work. hard work, you
know, just um seeing him like anything
that I wanted or, you know, um you know,
I saw him get up early for us to go get
that and for us to to have and um you
know, he's been l training, throwing
footballs at me since I was three years
old. So, I mean, you know, I he is the
reason, you know, I'm here today. um you
know just the leader and you know how
strong he is physically and mentally um
you know for us to to live out our
dreams. So you know definitely a lot of
love for him and you know don't take
that for granted as well.
>> You said this is home and we've seen in
these first few years how much you've
done in this at a community different
charities thing. What is it about
obviously this organization but the
community around it that really you know
endeared itself to you and made you want
to be here for a while to come now?
>> Yeah, I think it's a special place and a
place for you know growth and you know
me growing as a young man um um I just
fell in love with the city and and I
want the best you know for my community
and especially you know if I'm going to
lay my head here. So, you know, anything
I can do to help, you know, I will. And,
you know, John just gave me some more
opportunity to do so. So, um, definitely
appreciative of that in the city and,
you know, I can feel the love here. So,
just want to repay repay it back.
>> John, obviously a couple guys have
signed elsewhere, but in general, you it
seems like you really made a priority
resigning a lot of guys kind of dating
back to Charles in January and things
like that. Just how important has that
been this offseason just retains you
guys? Yeah, we've talked about it
before. Obviously, we want to keep as
many guys as we possibly can. You know,
it's
however you look at it. Fortunately or
unfortunately, that's it's just part of
the business. It's part of the job. Uh
that we've all, you know, jumped into
and, you know, we're going to miss the
guys that have left and and uh you know,
we're going to dive in even more to to
the guys that are still on our our team.
And we had planned for this. uh you know
uh you know like I said Joey Lane you
know in our group upstairs I mean we
we've been you know as as you approach
free agency free agency meetings what
that looks like uh getting through the
combine speaking to everybody down there
seeing what the landscape's going to
look like but obviously draft and retain
I mean this is a great example of of
drafting and developing and and and
keeping it in house and that's that's
that's that's
you know been our priority since uh
since we got here in 2010. So, um, that
that hasn't changed, but, uh, yeah, the
strategy of it was is, you know, trying
to extend our guys as much as we
possibly can. We have a cool mix of, you
know, guys that are just kind of hitting
their like their their their first time
in free agency and, you know, veterans
that have been through free agency
before and it's just a really cool mix
of like older and younger guys. So, it's
pretty neat. Mike, is how maybe
unexpected or pleasantly surprised are
you can bring most of this team a Super
Bowl champion? Most of it's coming back
for you to coach next year.
>> Well, it's great. We again, like John
said, you want as many people as back as
possible, but it was also um like John
said, these are things that we're trying
to plan for in advance. So, um it's
going to it's going to deviate a little
bit based off just the nature of the
business, but uh this is something
definitely we were hoping for and
planning for.
>> Yeah. talked before about what Cooper
meant to you. Then you guys resigned
Rasheed, resigned, resigned Bobo. Just
your position group. I know you're
close. Just how excited you have that
moment?
>> Excited to see the guys back. You know,
we know how special we are and you know
what we contribute to the team. You
know, each single one of us. So, um, and
like John said, just great people. You
know, love to work with them, respect
them, you know, on and off the field.
And you know, we're excited to to gear
up and get ready for our second year
together.
>> Have you had a Jackson, have you had a
chance to chat with Brian Flurry yet?
And where's your excitement with being
able to work with the new coordinator
this year?
>> Yeah, I said hello. Um, definitely
excited. Um, you know, definitely ready
to see, you know, what, you know, what
we're gunning towards and, you know,
just get in the same language and get
together. So, I'm excited for, you know,
new opportunities.
>> Mike, what are some things uh about
Jackson as like a person and a
competitor that you see all the time
behind the scenes that maybe we don't
see?
>> Be careful with this one.
>> Careful. I I think it's I think it's the
I think it's a unique combination of of
the ability
um the competitive spirit, but also like
the selflessness of who he is and how he
operates and how he goes about his
business. It's just it's a rare
combination outside of like whatever
position you say just just in life. I
mean, just having the having the having
the respect for the operation, the
people, your teammates, um the love that
he has for the people around him, no
matter their situation, but also being
just an absolutely high level competitor
when it when it's coming down to it and
uh
and the ability, you know, it's just
like this triple-headed monster of just
a really cool combination.
>> John, you love NFL history. I'm curious
if you see parallels with the former
great Seahawk and Steve Larent and great
rat runner, great hands person he was on
and off the field and and what you you
got here in Jackson.
>> Yeah, I think it's that's a that's
pretty awesome. Yeah, it's a
>> Yeah, I mean I didn't write a report on
Steve Larin or anything. Thanks, man. I
get it. But uh getting up there in age.
Um no, but uh it's a great question. And
I think uh yeah, I think that there's
like this cool I think combination
between, you know, Steve with the the
body control, you know, the hands, being
able to just be able to adjust to the
ball like down the field, the late
hands, all that. But also like Tyler and
Doug, too. There's a really I think
there's a really neat uh that's the
second time I use the word neat. Like
where's that coming from? Um just a
really cool combination of of just
different talents. And I just remember
we were we were so blessed like that he
was there at 20. Remember being at the
proday that day and we're like there's
no way we're going to like why are we
meeting with this guy like like what and
we're sitting there asking if he's going
to be a you know you know can you feel
pon he's looking at us like well
preceiver too you know like but
um no great question thanks for there's
a really the skill set is just really
unique and um
yeah um
I'm excited to see where he's going to
take this thing. You mentioned that
draft. I remember coming out of it. You
talked about how fortunate you felt to
be able to get Spoon and Jax kind of top
guys at both those positions. What was
that weight between five and 20 like
seeing him still out there?
>> Yeah, it took forever. I remember, you
know, I was probably driving Trent and
Matt Barry and Nolan, those guys
probably driving those guys crazy like
do we go up? Should we go up? Should we
go for him or, you know, like get a
little itchy, you know? Um
but we had just kind of studied like
okay well where uh like where like how
and when and so um yeah we just it felt
like it it literally felt like I don't
know three hours or something. So
changed my shirt a couple times.
>> Jackson in an interview before you said
uh my whole life I've taken stairs I've
had to prove myself. Is this contract
extension enough proof for you?
Yeah. I mean, I I've always had the
belief. Um, but yeah, this is Yeah, this
proves that, you know, I'm good for for
a long time. You know what I'm saying?
Like, so I guess that's what it proves
and makes me definitely feel good and,
you know, it's a blessing.
>> Yeah.
>> Last question.
>> Um, you mentioned Jody at the top of
your comments. Obviously, the team's for
sale and all that, but I know you guys
had said business as usual and
everything come in. This obviously seems
like proof of it. I mean, um approving
her approving a big deal like this.
>> Yeah, absolutely. You know, she's
>> she's like, "Let's go win another one,
you know, let's get after it." So, you
know, um there's another world out there
that, you know, is coming. We're getting
ready for it. But, uh as of right now,
man, we're just we'll just keep ripping
like uh like we always have.
>> All right. Thank you everyone. Thank
you.